Once we have our instructions created,
一旦制作好了指南
which will be an iterative process as you go through your data and find more edge cases,
PS: 随着你更深入地了解数据 或者 找到更多极端例子 你就需要更新指南
we can go into the quality.
我们可以继续进入“Quality”（质量）页面
So you want us to create a set of test questions
在这里可以创建一些测试问题
for your job which is essentially ground truth data.
这些测试问题会有标准答案 可以作为测试标准
It's where you provide an answer to the question,
你将为每个测试问题标出正确答案
and the contributor is working in the job are tested on these answers,
人工标注专家们在承接任务以及执行任务时
both before entering and while they continue to work.
都需要通过这个测试 才能继续做任务
This ensures that they understand what they're doing,
这样可以保证他们清楚地了解需要做什么
it ensures that their accuracy keeps up.
也保证了准确率
If they ever fall below the accuracy threshold that you set,
一旦他们的准确率低于你设定的最低值
they get removed from the job.
他们就会被移出任务
So we'll go into the quality page,
进入到 Quality 页面
we will create a new test question,
创建一个新的测试问题
click out of these messages.
关掉这些弹窗
So in this job in this particular image,
对于这个任务的这个图像
we can see that there are no parking signs,
我们可以看到没有停车标志
so we would want to select no.
所以答案是 - 否
We also want to include a reason.
我们需要提供原因
So when a contributor misses a test question,
如果人工标注专家选错了
they are shown the correct answer after they submit,
在提交后 他们可以看到正确答案
along with a reason for why they were incorrect.
以及他们错误的原因
So in this case, the answer is no,
对于这个图像 答案是否
we'll say this image only contains houses.
原因是 - 这个图像仅包含了房屋
So this is a chance for you to train the contributors while they're working.
提供错误原因可以帮助你更好地训练你的人工标注团队
If you don't include a reason,
如果你不提供错误原因
they won't necessarily understand why they were wrong,
他们可能就不知道哪里错了
and it doesn't help them learn to look out for what they missed previously.
而且下次遇到同样的情况 也还是会犯同样的错误
So we'll go ahead and save this.
完成以后 点击保存
So one thing to note about test questions is you do
设计测试问题的一个注意点是
want to make sure you have a pretty even answer distribution.
你需要保证你的问题答案类别是大致平衡的
So if we take a look here,
比如 看这里
we've got about 59 percent no.
答案是否的问题比例为 59%
Because we only have two answer options,
因为我们的问题只有两个答案选项
we can choose to make this closer to 50/50.
所以 答案为否的问题 与答案为是 的问题 比例应该尽量接近 50:50
This is to ensure a couple of things.
有几个原因
So one, we want to make sure that
首先 我们希望
you're testing contributors on all possible answer types,
人工标注人员能接触到所有可能的答案类型
and you're not training them to lean more towards no,
以及 你没有训练他们去偏向于任何一个答案 比如否
there's no parking sign.
没有停车标志
So you want to train them to look out for everything that might appear in your dataset.
你需要训练他们 让他们熟悉数据集里所有可能的图像类型
This is also to ensure quality from contributors.
这是为了保证标注的质量
Let's say you had a 90 percent no,
假设 高达 90% 的测试问题的答案都是否
that would really allow people to just select
那么 人们很可能每次就闭着眼选否
no every time and continue to work in the job.
然后 还可以通过测试 继续做任务
Once you have enough test questions created,
一旦你创建了足够多的测试问题
you can go ahead and launch the job.
你就可以发布任务了
We always recommend launching just a subset of the data,
建议每次都发布一部分数据
this is to ensure you don't launch
这是因为 一旦你发布了整个数据集
your entire job and then realize that something was wrong with your instructions,
然后意识到你的指南、测试问题、设计或者数据集本身有错误
or your test questions, or the design, or the data itself.
那么就很麻烦了
So you should default to launching a 100 rows
默认每次先发布 100 个数据行
to begin with and as the job is running, you can monitor.
然后在任务开展的同时 进行监测
So this job is already been launched so we'll take a look at the monitor page.
因为这个任务已经发布了 所以我们直接去"monitor"（监测）页面
We can see high-level numbers here for how the job ran,
可以看到任务的整体情况和一些概括性数据
we can see how many contributors failed out of quiz mode.
以及有多少人工标注人员未通过测试
While the job is running, you should also go back and look at your test questions.
在任务进行的同时 也需要关注测试问题的数据
So going back into quality,
回到 quality 页面
it helps to take a look at the most highly missed questions,
看一下错误率最高的测试问题 可以帮助理解
and see where contributors are misunderstanding the job.
为什么这些人会选错
So again, this is another opportunity for you to identify what's going
再次强调 这是个很好的机会 可以让你了解任务哪里进展不顺
wrong in the job and where you may need to
以及你是否需要优化指南
augment the instructions or include more examples,
或者提供更多示例
or maybe you need to redesign your job.
还是需要重新设计任务
Something could have gone terribly wrong.
有时候 可能会发现大问题
So in this case,
看下这个测试问题
we said the answer is yes,
正确答案为 是
there's a parking sign in this image,
图像包含停车标志
but 86 percent of contributors were wrong.
但是 高达 86% 的人都选错了
So we can see based on our reason,
问题的错误原因里写道：
that there's no parking sign on the left side.
在左边有一个“禁止停车”标志
So we can see up here,
往上看
in the middle like center left,
中间往左
there is a no parking sign,
有一个“禁止停车”标志
we want to make sure contributors notice that.
我们希望引起人工标注人员的注意
It is really small,
标志很小
it is easy to miss,
很容易漏掉
but we want to make sure our model can
但是我们希望确保模型是可以识别
understand there are signs in this image, we want to catch this.
这种类型的标志
So what the contributors miss,
如果人工标注人员漏掉了
your model may also miss.
模型肯定也无法识别出
So this would be an opportunity for us to potentially even take this particular image,
所以 这是一个信号 我们应该在指南里增加这个图像作为示例
which again is why instructions are an iterative process.
因此 制作指南是一个不断迭代的过程
You may find you only covered
你可能会发现自己只包括一些常见的简单示例
simpler cases and you want to go back and include more difficult ones.
所以需要返回去 添加更多示例